Before we paint on the glass, we're going to clean the glass, so we have to get to the glass.
So we're just going to take the back of this frame out and remove the paper and the various things that come with it.
And be careful when you work with glass, especially these glasses in the frames, because unlike this glass door over here, this glass that comes with this is really thin.
So what I'm going to do is just very gingerly, carefully remove the glass and just set it on the cardboard.
And then I'm going to set the frame to the side just for a second while I clean it, and just take your--any glass cleaner will do fine.
You don't need a ton, just like one little spray, and then just clean the glass so we have a nice surface to work on.
Your paper towels will probably try to run away, but that's all right.
Okay, and then once you get that side, you can flip to the other side.
The frames in the stores tend to collect a lot of dust and fingerprints and so forth.
So I'm just going to hit one spray on this side.
Just get all the streaks out.
All right.
And then once the glass is clean, I'm just going to try and keep my grubby fingertips off of it.
Set that there, bring the frame back into the frame--no pun intended--and then I'm just going to set this back in there, like that.
Ta-da, and that's cleaning the glass for painting.